There are teams, yes, this is our route.
There are a lot of four of them again, but let's get the personal answers.
Is that five?
Three, two, one.
There's seven, nine.
That's five.
Five.
Six.
So, the business of B&E, the business of closing this agenda.
Seven.
Trust the community of South Wales.
And eight.
The journalists.
What's open?
Five.
Now, we'll talk more of the great for meeting.
The United States Council for March 1st.
I think 21.
Number.
Nine of them.
Two.
Proclamation.
It's like March.
National.
The nutrition.
We don't know.
Jordan Valley.
They haven't.
China.
We're.
I think.
It's.
We're.
Also,
we're.
We're.
This is a.
Well, now.
So, this year's theme is actually personal eyes or plates.
We know there's not a one-size-fits-all approach to nutrition, or health, or a well-me.
We're all different.
We have their background, we have different lines, different schedules.
We have different taste preferences.
So, we are hoping to be able to officially declare
more intersectional nutrition rather than mine.
So, that we can interact with the restaurants in the library
and one of the girls club to put out these programs this month to help people
do just that to personalize and play.
So, we kind of brought me to the table.
One of the programs that...
we need to partner with a rational arts year in town, so we, if the rational arts
wants to participate, we're just gonna be asked even to put this little first line
of playing national interest in month of love over the moon with those, so the community knows
that they are participating in the program with us. Particularly some of the suggestions
for getting to the rational arts are to hand out his colored pages all of those on nutrition
to the kids that come in to eat, they'll get trained into the courts. And then we're hoping
that the rational arts will maybe not totally tweak them in you, but just encourage the kids
and adults to instead of like you can first rise to a career of actual, and if they do that
we have a ton of little toys that we're gonna get to the rational arts so that they pick the kids
and pick those out and have fun with it. We actually run an example today for the mayor and her
who's kind of tough on specials and the rest of the council members to try out the um
so if you type of vegetable, we have a really colorful mustache for you, we actually brought
me some deartiness as hourly vegetables, which was basically like a couple of vegetables. So this is
me cold on the assignment or beside the court. Anyway, if you wanted to have an enjoy it,
but if you would fill in you want to try it so we would have had a group to have.
Can you tell me if I put it in the conversation that the mayor tries to be vegetables that we wouldn't get it past?
Yeah, I would like to add um we are focusing a lot on the children that we are going to try to
encourage adults to take more about for choices throughout this month. So in order for these
your type of health system we're going to have an adult window and yeah, they can participate in throughout
the month and far off different fruits and vegetables and are on there.
and activities like participated in to earn incentives that we might like to result.
So I would like to, is that opportunity to the employees of the city in Miami,
if that's something that the VIs, we was in one of the coordinates that,
and because the VNoShe needed to give us something that was had different fruits of vegetables that even eat.
We've read activities like walk on a tractor and community, go outside and play with your children, things like that,
and so we have some meat, garden, incentives, and just by their things.
Cook folks that we would like to make a mouthful to city employees,
if that's not the city would be interested in coordinating with us.
I don't know, I mean, it's not that everyone has to participate,
but we just like my channel about all the things some of the city employees are like to do.
Thank you.
We think of that, I think our HR director would like to do that.
Yeah, this happened in Illinois, I thought we were going to get that.
What's that? Any questions?
Still, we need a motion to make more of some natural nutrition work.
Okay, I'm so late.
I'm not going to do that.
I'm not going to do it, sure.
All right.
Now, there are four.
There is all the mayor barker in the opposite council.
Do you hear about it right now?
The march is national nutrition level.
Within the city of Miami, they encourage all of this.
This is the joint campaign to jump in the turn about the nutrition and nutrition of others.
You know, the chief, the hot morning health, both the day and the warm.
The three of them get put and let's get a little personal care.
Not those speaking, get three minutes.
The mayor of the council will allow us to go on.
The reason we're going to go on is because it could be a violation of those things that.
It'll be like the action needs to be on a future agenda.
I don't know what we'll do that at that time.
And I'll speak of the day to just flip.
I'm going to have to go there for a future.
You guys.
So the time to hear it slide to your question.
The city of Miami.
and statistics for FYI 15, 16, while I started following June 17, 2016.
In July 2016, the whole form of e-counseling, scattered as a line, had from all of the
statistics that later piled up on June 12, 11, 17, lawsuit also alleges that Orange was
the accounting worker engaged in formal audit, so I'm going to need to cancel with this
year's 24th of 2015, and for each audit of year, I'm going to need to clean the quality
of it.
That the financial position, both of us see the lawsuit further away, is that after a thorough
investigation, we came clear that Orange is auditing and sorting correct and misleading.
The knowledge of fields are reasonably apart from the form of risk assessment of OECD.
The knowledge of FOI can act with the FOI of odd planning and testing procedures in the
farthest fields, with form of audits and accordance with reasonable and abnormal audit
in the same groups.
The lawsuit seeks to recover on damages caused by colleges conduct.
I reached out to them today, and they said that the lawsuit has been selling out food, and that
they no longer have them held for their services.
I also found that the city is going to hire them to investigate part of water chargers to the
government.
While a lot of it came back clean, I'm kind of reminded that the service of the ones who
don't promote e-counts was wrong.
I would like to know that the city is under current contract for the research that is in the
so far at all.
I would like to know that the city knows of our original employees in that equipment, a lot of odd planning,
and testing procedures that were registered in OECD's lawsuit in 2017, and, again, I ask
that the city will have a quick mental and ultimate source for all the services that are
under current circumstances.
Thank you, Judge.
From the floor, we can sit in a different separate remains to be approved by the five and six
in the community.
From seven, presentation from monetary and economic development services to the Charlotte
faculty.
We need everyone, and we're all doing well.
And someone to update you a little bit of our needs, of course we'll include a little bit of our
development education, and then what we've been doing well.
So this is a little bit of what our focus is for 2021 this year we have a strategic plan in place and our four areas of focus will be business
Retention and Expansion or course entrepreneurship and recruitment of point out. There we go.
First of all, I want to say thank you to the city for your continued partnership and support.
We also wanted to address a little bit about what the city funds are designated for within our budget just to kind of give you guys an idea of what we
need, line and hide on that nine and four. So one of the things that we've done this year is to make sure that people know what the city and
the funds are going towards.
One of those would be accounting at CleadsArt, audits as well as we're going to be getting quarterly and dependent financial reports.
And number two is advertising. This is our website site consultant publications for the last year for years.
We haven't been advertising in these and we used to, they're an important part of economic development.
And so it's something that we want to call locally to partner with the state of the issue.
Also, due to the subscriptions, this includes the Obelham Economic Development Council and the Governors Economic Development Marketing team, which is actually combined now and turned into the Obelham and select Obelham.
What this group does is it's a group of economic development organizations throughout the state that pay their dues and participate in setting
policy for economic development, but also for best practices. So one of the things we'll do is travel some of us will try to
balance with who we're supposed to be during the next farm to meet with consultants and talk a little bit about what will come in that we have to offer.
Another thing they do, they offer and the site consultant took to New York, I don't know if you can do that one.
And they go in culture, it's like we make this repair operations for errors, which is one of the biggest aerospace companies in New York.
I've been in that show several years, never seen Obelham a non-closed deal with that shit.
And so we feel like it's important for making my image to be a part of those organizations to help continue to do best practices for economic development, but also to keep my Emma on everyone's radar and what we have to do.
Insurance is something that's my guide over the city funds, and then repairs and maintenance on our own.
If anyone ever has questions about those, please feel free to come by and we'll sit down and go through getting a guide that you like this to.
So first, what we do business retention expansion, that's code talking basically for protecting what you have.
75% of the growth, you guys can be saying this all the time.
75% of your growth comes from what you already have available. So how can we take care of those companies and those employers that we have now?
For maids, we're focusing on manufacturing the course, but we also work with back office services, even our restaurants to say, hey, can't possibly help you.
So this year, we assisted it over 273.
thousand dollars in the Oklahoma Business Relate Program, which is what the Oklahoma Youth
Summit are carefitting for. Businesses could apply, it was almost like PPP. We help
apply businesses with that. We hosted the Executive Director of Brent Kisling from the Department
of Commerce on two industry tumors and a reception with those recipients as well as Oklahoma
Review Residence. Which, Miami got a little over $200,000, and that as well for community
manufacturers. We did the Oklahoma Department of Agriculture Awarding Coach Processing $200,000
for their expansion, which includes several jobs, and we continue to facilitate them with financing,
workforce, and even personnel guidelines to help their expansion succeed in growing. And
then we also worked with local infrastructure on an expansion project of about $2 million.
We were able to put them in touch with the finance authority and get them packing and
packing in one of our global tribes through their financial institution. Sorry, it's a little
small there. We've been working with a look, and I'm sorry I can't even be specific to you guys
now that worked from a new and economic development. Most of the companies says it's okay, you'll
not hear the companies name, and I don't know. A lot of times they need to be confidential. We facilitated
meetings with the local manufacturer in state and local resources for a large expansion in the
Miami area. This is still happening. Sometimes it's still take a while, but would be for an average
way to around $15 an hour, but also would be able to benefit some of our businesses that are already in
the community because they are a local supplier. So they would be able to supply a particular ingredient
that one of our manufacturers need to make their product. We're still working on that one, but we did
set up meetings with them for R&D with the new Product Development Center as well as the Oklahoma
Advancement for Science and Technology. We worked with the retail business with long-term
expansionists to facilitate a meeting again with Oklahoma Finance Authority. We were able to get them
in SBAM. We also assisted them with Oklahoma manufacturing alliance, and they were doing their report
at our facility on Thursday. What this does is that any of you have a business, particularly
manufacturing, where you need to make factory lines to come out, they will do it for your assessment.
They come in here at the facility. They ask you and some of your leader tips and questions.
And then they talk through the assessment with you and give you best practices to help streamline
their process. During the first round of the panel of tech and program, I received well over $2 million
in assistance. We actually worked with 25 companies directly on their application. This included some of them
to a clock in the morning, because that's the only time we could get logged in. The first round was pretty intense.
On the second round, we've not had as many of businesses apply. We assisted 10 in the last two months,
as well as four companies with the economic injury disaster level. There are COVID-19 funding available for businesses.
Most of it is not bringing more except for the payroll protection.
program that if you need help with something like that, give us a call and let's talk and see
what resources are available for your business.
We will be getting made monthly manufacturing meetings for the volume of region.
These used to happen through the Green Country Manufacturing Council and they stopped a couple
years ago.
We want to put them back in place and this will be a form for manufacturers to talk to
each other, not for me to talk to them.
At the reason we want to do this is sometimes they don't realize if they haven't
run them on back yard and they can make deals together and say together.
We're also going to be doing a new committee for business retention expansion.
We're trying to set the day for that today.
We'll be sending that out to some people that are interested in serving on that committee.
If you are interested, let me know.
What we want this committee to do is to be people that are comfortable going out to manufacturers
at least twice a year asking them some pretty basic questions so that we can see what trends
are affecting our employers in the region and if they're ways that we can help them.
Then Knights will be hosting the Oklahoma Department of Commerce's Aces team.
We'll be in an additional two potential companies that we think that they can help in the region
and this is the team that focuses on other space.
Strategic Workforce.
This is one of the biggest issues for employers right now to face the American.
We have worked with consistently with our 20- where you resource partners in the region
as well as hosting job fairs in several locations.
We are now that is turned into a monthly regional recap where we're all working together to try to find employers.
We are also participating in a four-counting Workforce Program and hosted our first meeting in February with the Scott Fry,
the Director of Workforce for Mid-America, talking to us a little bit about a Center for Excellence,
which is the state's credibility program.
So basically if you do the work and you can put together a strategic plan to show you potential employers of workforce,
you can get accredited as a Center for Excellence.
This is a big deal to cite and told us because they know that if you're a Center for Excellence,
you have everything ready to know for their pertains for clients.
We'll be having those meetings every quarter.
A lot of those people that are participating on that committee are our anti-capital resources in the area
because that is key to work work right now.
As a member of the Governor's Economic Development, are the Oklahoma folks like Oklahoma,
we have I've been appointed to the Marketing Committee.
This is not just to recruit me businesses, but we're going to be looking at marketing ways about how great it is to live in Oklahoma.
Because of COVID we've seen a lot of interest in people that come work remotely and we want to tell them that my name is great place to work.
We also partnered with the Claremore Economic Industrial Economic Development Authority in America,
the Northeast Workforce Board, Tulsa, Portitusia, and Nora, the Northeast Oklahoma Regional Line Alliance to submit an Oklahoma Worksector Partnership grant.
This was to provide some kind of good road back and answer our excellence.
to start putting that pipeline in place and make sure that our educational systems are meeting the needs of our employers.
We did not be a factory with his family, but the group has decided to continue our efforts and work together
and include the Board of Muscovi to see if we can put some kind of regional plan in place where everybody is not using their own resources for each individual plane.
Entrepreneurship, I don't know what's going on, but they are coming out of the woodwork in Miami with his great.
We assisted in over 25 entrepreneurs in 2020, several different industries across the board.
We did receive an expansion into our revolving one thing.
This is not granted. We received what this is, is that if we have a business that needs a loan, we have that with more money to loan.
In 2021, when we will start our entrepreneurship committee, that will be some time in arms for April.
For April, again, if you're interested in letting out, the goal of this committee is to look at those practices and how we can continue to encourage that community in Miami with things like the mentorship program.
When we get business owners to commit to one hour and a month to talk to entrepreneurs about what's good and what's that.
The other thing we do is something like a little part 10.
You know, a total of a 100,000 dollar chart 10.
We're committed to companies who come in, and if they have this idea, they wouldn't have heard that.
Well, could Miami be a product or 10,000?
Get the community involved to support our entrepreneurs.
We picked up two new memberships this year from our entrepreneurs, and we'll start a marketing campaign on our shared space.
In January, February alone, we have a VISTA assisted over 15 entrepreneurs on business clients.
So I don't know if it's COVID, I don't know if what it is, but everybody's got a great idea.
We wanted to try to help them with the end of our business.
And this is the big one.
We're preparing for a few year projects.
We did over 20 art piece last year, which was response for proposals.
We did have a new business open in the old ice house.
We've facilitated them with our state business status as well as meeting with local resources.
The city has worked very closely with them as well.
And basically, they take the leather from Southwest Airlines seats and recycling into bags that they can sell online.
And they've got a lot of other rights to do.
I think they're going to try to be quite a few things.
But they work with high-address, under-employed employees, and they've got to scale them in the life.
So we're helping to do a ribbon cutting with them to suit.
We have attended our fight training because the responses are getting more and more complicated.
They're doing a lot quicker than they used to be.
The last one I got, so I guess one I've ever seen.
And we got it all perfect and it's due to market.
So any kind of training we can do like that when the state provides it for free.
We're going to go.
We hosted two companies last year with long-term plans of this patient.
And we're hoping in Miami.
And then we also did, we were going to do a luncheon.
and one of our local realtors has been right and that this sponsor us.
With the realtors to talk about how we can make sure everyone knows what's available in money and not,
we have to postpone that because of the COVID that we're hoping to get that we're leaning in the same.
And then we'll be coordinating with the Governor's team Aces and the Department of Commerce for a future opportunity
with site consultants and treaches.
May 2st, is it's last year where the companies actually came in to look at Brian and that leads us to this.
And some of you may know that last week we want a project with over a few hundred jobs in the first year for a local call center.
I can tell you some of the details that weren't included in this.
The starting way is 11 dollars an hour.
There are bonuses just for showing up.
And then there will be commissions as well.
It isn't in that call center. These are not the people that call you during the time.
These are people that are getting customer service and running memberships or canceling memberships.
The company told me today and we're the most helpful day of our kind of community.
At the city partnered with us and we're very closely with us to make them feel welcome.
We were able to find an information.
They wanted to be in Miami don't give me wrong.
They definitely wanted to be in Miami but we were up against another community in Missouri.
We were able to show them that we really wanted to be here and we had some opportunities available for them.
They call this last week to let us know.
We'll have the jobs hopefully filled in the next year.
And that is it.
Anybody have any questions?
Thank you guys.
Thank you, sir.
Number eight.
At least at least on three minutes out of the main.
To give it a call and then we'll show them the instructions.
We're going to be sitting on a gal.
I'm just curious.
Yes.
So we've come to the house before.
And we've gone through this process.
And this is something when we're approached by a system.
What's the purpose of our meeting?
The moment or here is the property that that means to happen with.
We have come to the council and asked if you could release the loans at the city hallways.
And sometimes we need to go through these.
So in this case.
The city has a faded property twice for a total of $16 dollars.
There was a severe structure fire.
In December of 2020.
This has been vacant for a part of our lives.
We've run out of ignorance.
The property is set up in different times.
The property is conferred to us by Eli Chinnamas.
The role is the merit compensation that's two.
One property over from 3.7.
He plays.
and I'll just put for the structure with possible reuse of it
as a personal one.
We're working with him to understand if that's feasible or not,
but either way he's what he's willing to do most of the property.
And I'll cost the city approximately $36 to release the lanes.
And there, we would possibly look at doing a tipping fee waiver
at a later date whenever I started to demo it,
that he costs about $600 in the city manager
has to withdraw into doing those tipping fees.
That's not something that has to come back into total.
And if we cost the city approximately $4,000 to demolish
the structure of if there's no respect in the past.
So it's the cost savings to the city to help the citizens go ahead
and manage the property.
We have got the calls from the citizens when the city is going
forward and do something.
We can act immediately on a structure fire,
a house that's pile of fire because we haven't given time.
We're the insurance to act early and we've got to go through
the normal state statute of requirements and the company here.
Just believe in it.
I'll select you.
All right.
You guys.
Who is I?
Thank you.
Not a discussion about the vote.
The use of the 0.65 percent self tax collection.
I would love to go to the district manager of the department
for a street improvement project.
Let's do this.
OK.
So because I know there's something here.
I don't know where to go.
I just a little bit.
I want to talk about the street sales tax.
What's the 65 sales tax in the city?
What's the 65 sales tax?
Back on May 12, 2009, the council goes to the proposal
for the citizens at her advisory meeting.
Actually, I met and they went with one cent sales tax online.
That was voted down by the citizens.
And the advisory meeting got back together again.
They proposed to the council.
They asked them to put a 0.65 sales tax to the citizens.
That was a period on July 27, 2010.
That said, it was a result of violence.
We got 12,000, 4,500,000 dollars.
The following period.
The sales tax, 1.65 sales tax, kind of,
sales tax, kind of, sales tax.
So as soon as that $2,000,500,000 dollars was paid off,
there is no.
That gets the 65 sales tax in the world.
A few years later, a citizen's advisor
can be paying for what the council was asked for.
And to thank the proposal to the citizens to extend that point six five sales tax to include repairs to the second.
That was proposed to the citizens that I did vote for it on, let's see, May 12, but you, I'm sorry, February 12, 2019.
So the point six five was approved for streets in 2010 and 2013 to extend that to include a $8.8 million repair for the state.
Okay, so now we have the point six high sales tax we had since, no, we collect so much so currently we collect on the point six five about a hundred and three thousand dollars a month.
On bond payments, that is a combined bond payment of the street fancy again is a $83,000 and some change.
So there's about $20,000 worth of enrichment.
Well that sets it off on and collects.
There are three things we can do is that when we can, there's a Jew can do that.
You can pay off on or you can do street repairs or you can do safety repairs.
Tonight we're asking that you take $24,000 dollars of that money that's collecting in the fund and use it for road and road.
So the history of that money that collects that we collect over what was spent on bonds.
The history of what the council has approved to spend is right here.
So in January 23 of 2018, the council approved a hundred and $10,000.
You can see it's in your pocket.
A hundred and $80,500 for the honors cause at the state and they turned around that same year June during the budget season.
They approved a hundred and twenty seven for a road repair.
During the budget season of 2019, they approved an additional 240,000 for road repair.
And as of, we're estimating that the hundred and three of them tell me that we're collecting every month.
That's a very conservative number by now because we are still sex is doing very well.
We believe that it would be the estimated conservative estimate is about $251,000 as a June 30th of this year, 21.
We are, it's not here to let you know that we believe there's that there's $200,000 available for road repair.
And that's what the street has available.
It's a part of what we would like to do with that money.
Do you have any questions?
So the total amount of the bonds was that we combined the street and the street bonds with the stadium bonds back in 2016.
We had about 19 million left to pay.
That goes in, I think, at home we took, I think to 2,026.
So any additional money to be collected in that time, you can operate forward the things that they were originally for.
Unless you want to pay off the bonds themselves.
Did I answer your question?
Okay.
I'd like to be.
Good idea.
It's a discussion of possible love to be done there.
Our pleasure to be able to get from our partners going to talk about what to do,
rather than to be busy with the affairs.
I'm going to show you about it.
I think you're still in the back.
So we want to make it if you agree to do that.
We don't want to talk about the horrors.
We've already agreed for money.
To budget the money for the program.
Of course, you need to talk whenever that happens.
And then you agree with the contracts.
Once you have a money, you'll be in the office.
I'd like to share the project to be able to be out.
And I want to try to do that.
Normally, we had a project in the last year that we were meeting.
Mail and over there.
And there's no way around the hospital in the trees that we did about the turn of the
house streets because it's about 1.7 million now.
We're going to do about turn of the house of the tree territory.
We'll need to learn in 404 that.
That's a little different concept.
Instead of the million, you'll let us all agree with the asshole and it's stable.
We do a concept for the little cracks, he'll want to only have cracks here and possible.
and then they use it for it to either make a mix
and they will cover the best trees,
which we're hoping to make them save another five to 10 years.
To go back and re-build it to that main tree,
it would be one hundred million miles.
So we're hoping this two hundred and forty-fourth out of that building.
We extend the line to these trees,
and these are the trees here.
Central, these are the general, these trees and northeast,
and then the south part of Main Street
is not being regionized by the map.
So it will be completely totally black.
You start being here, and then so the third is,
you won't go far, it'll only a fifth at noon
with all the same.
It's a part of you do the green,
and you allocate this to the money to do so.
You have a point to hear it?
Yeah.
This is, this is a scope of that.
You'll hear it if you're back at noon.
Yeah.
There's a trade, so how many's per yards?
And some charging there, this was the band that we received, only three different companies.
I'm not sure if you can see the top one.
It was a company as of a little sale of Texas.
It was 380,000 approximately.
The bottom company is mass brothers at the Kansas City.
We've got it in several different times.
Do you work here in Miami?
They actually did a job for high-harons at the apartment at the airport.
Which, you know, when they're in the airport too.
I believe that's why they're being quite a bit lower.
They'll make the hell a feed when they can't deny it.
And they grow the fuel lower because they're already coming to Miami.
Again, it's 224,000, 130,000,000 less.
That's something Gilles already talked to you about the 103,000 months of 2010, 244.
I think our beer is exactly 244,600.
My name is $4,000.
Again, it's hopefully you'll have to say that you don't have miles of trees.
We're going to have to put in the revision.
And then right now we need a block across the city where from the 50 to 80,000.
And you know, how wide under the company, you know, the last half set like that.
So a block takes a little bit of a block to make miles.
You know, there's a few of that.
Again, I think you'll have to read that one.
Do you want to read that one?
You'll read it.
So I'm just going to read off these streets.
You might not be able to see them up there.
So it's going to be central from D Street or Drekground all the way to the high school.
Yes.
That's going to be south main from Steve Ontholvar to 1st or 2st or 1st.
I'm going to sign up for this.
Hey, I'm inside the streets.
Hey.
Oh, that.
I wanted to hang on any more.
I'll be good job from Maine, the J North West.
Correct.
And then B Street or D Street between BJ Council and 12 Street.
That's correct.
That's to an amount of that.
That's a one more thing.
I'd like you to be done.
So we'll come with you.
The members are proposing.
Please, a reserve of three months.
So any 3,000 times.
Sorry.
It leaves that as a reserve.
It's too long.
In second case, something happened to have three months.
Any questions for Robert and Jill?
So now I would like to make the motion to amend the 211-19.
First, you have to do a little bit.
Do that.
You need to accept or reject the status of the recommendation of the United States.
Don't you do 114 in?
Watch out.
Yeah.
Great.
Don't be a motion to accept or reject the 211-19.
Let's treat it in the screen to stay in the morning.
How about?
I'll second it.
We'll take a time.
Please take a time.
Pardon?
Now I'm 11.
We have to accept or reject the status of the recommendation.
We'll do a little bit of a number of C-20-187.
For a street recruitment to advance the brothers in the amount of 244,000,800,
or a six-on-a-n-a-four dollars.
We'll do a little bit of a number of C-20-177.
I'll try to take a minute.
I'm going to continue to on the installation of a fire.
It's not going to be a group of citymen reported that there's a need to sign.
Notice, the two perceived.
I'll make a motion.
I'll approve.
How's it going?
Pardon?
I'll go ahead.
Do we want to go ahead?
Yeah.
I'll go ahead.
and receive 20 tax 9-1 for the test gate system to test court and amount of 48-9-5-1-7-1-1-1-1-1-4-3-6.
We've purchased with plenty of systems.
The system's to 55-9-1, we're going to buy a file file.
Chief of a Rucket, didn't even know I had to do it.
And we were approved for a grant from the federal government for the system's firefighter grant, the purchase of cascades system,
which is the system with bills or breeding packs with air and pressurizes with the claims that we've been removed from the water.
The $52,000 test court is out of policy.
We use them on our current technical rescue trailer, the end of the four-wheel-cats gate.
And we've had more of the service with them.
Our bid was $1,000 more than the lowest, but our service work is cheaper because test court's out of policy and health fire, 700 plus miles away.
So our recommendation is to go with test court.
Do you have any of the tax-living from all of County people
who have to pay that additional $2,900?
I couldn't hear you.
Okay, all the election.
In the lot of County tax-living from the firefighters
that can be at every year from our County taxes
is there for the additional $2,400
just coming from that, is that correct?
That's correct.
Yeah.
We've said the sign on that.
Okay.
We're five percent.
So five percent.
Okay.
Thank you.
When you work with tax-living more?
Yes.
But actually, her horrible credit was announced.
And they, we had felt them in private expenses.
And they didn't get it fixed.
So the tax-living also serves as a portion of that by the way.
I make them absolutely accepted that you go with just for a new case.
Okay.
Oh, second.
The law, sir.
No.
I've never read a sign.
I've had it.
Now that we've got it.
Can you tell us a little bit about the grant?
I mean, was it hard to get?
Was it.
It was at the first time that we tried.
I appreciate her help.
We've applied probably three times.
But in the past, we have also added another, you know, other items that we needed.
And we took a class on grant writing for the AFG.
And they recommended that we pick one thing that you really, really need to go after it.
Instead of all the things.
And this time when we applied it.
That's what we knew we were able to get the grant.
Thank you.
I thought it was a perfect time to help with you at all.
We could build up the bottles.
I'm trying to work with you.
And they were available.
If we needed to find it.
Unless we had it.
May you respond.
Correct.
We were using that.
We were able to gather.
We needed to do several.
And there was probably a couple of times.
We exhausted it.
What we said.
We said waiting for a fillet.
We ran out there.
It was four or five bottles.
And we were able to.
We were able to build it up.
Good.
Okay.
Whatever.
Thank you.
And you all.
We're 13.
Another new business that may have risen.
So it's supposed to have the agenda.
Mayor.
Council.
Community.
Assembly.
Sen.
May.
Thank you, Mr. Mayor.
So, a couple things I would like to share with the Council tonight.
First off, I would like to thank the banks for the assurance of all of their work,
and the credit for our due employer that we've been laying in the outside of the yard.
But communication solutions can bring in their jobs, the entire area.
That is something that is really exciting.
I think to take that opportunity to really turn this into something great.
I think they start to start the role in the opening opportunities.
Additionally, I want to thank Charlotte in the heard room.
As the new city manager, and I think there's a specific, specific, specific number of their work of names.
They've just been very fonding, very transparent, and gave me a lot more of it.
Next thing I'd like to mention is to provide a reminder that it's working.
We have to bring it up to me.
So this year, we've got our Citywide Spring Cleanup.
It is March 22nd for the North West, South West, and March 29th for the North East.
In South East, we'll be putting this information out on social media and the website.
It's hoping that the Spring Workers can do their job.
This is their opportunity to get things dragged and heard.
The amount of airs you can just pick up and hold off to push the smooths.
You know, which brings me up in the yard waiting to find the things in the hallways that you can't fit in the hall of the doctor.
This is the opportunity to get out there and do the University of Cleanup.
Thirdly, I'd like to maybe talk about something obviously more critical for the future of one of us.
So we don't lose sight of where we're at, and I know it's not in the walls, as we've had our performance.
We've got to talk about it so that we can repair and work through the challenges that are probably yet to come.
I think everybody knows that we do need spring temperatures.
We can pretty much expect that we're going to have some feedback to our utility bills.
That's what we're across the board.
I would do want to make sure that we won't have anybody knows that at this time any increase that anyone sees their utility bill is solely due to the information they were using.
So just because it was extremely cold, we were ready to run up the park.
He usually is usually worth trying to combat that extremely cold.
There is not that price change to a fill up hour anyway.
So when they look at those bills, they have to realize that's the situation that we've
been saying.
Now, that being said, we're also doing everybody can read the paper about the impact
that the National Gas crisis, the family industry, the challenges that a lot of the utility
producers, the power producers have had in the extreme costs that they had to bear during
that time.
I mean, that's the reality of things that just right we have companies that, you know,
who do you need, I think, have some of their other billion dollars that they spend
with National Gas.
And while these companies are trying very hard to not well figure out how to spread that
past costs out over a year in a decade, I think, and we've developed my academic data account
from the GRDA, the GRDA is not the same type of utility as an OGP, but it was really
overseeing high reward by the legislature.
And they have yet to be able to determine what solution they're there and what it's like.
So at this time, we really don't know the full impact we've been going to have on my end of our
business.
Now, we'll tell you that they continue to tell us that they were in a position of 20 years
long, that they have a very robust rate of stabilization count.
Now, I'm hearing that rate of stabilization count is in place for just such events, so that
they can sort of take in those kind of bits and recruit that money back in a time.
But they have not yet been able to take solution that they're going to replace it, so we just
don't know what's going to do with the test.
Now, they haven't regularly scheduled to work in March 10, and once we're working here, they will
likely have to have a special meeting, and I assume that it's more March 10.
So, we're coming to the same point.
I'm going to be determined about the argument that came within, bring it to take.
There's no less about thanks to the information that they get it, but they just don't have
to do that.
I'm feeling really interesting, but they're constantly working the event.
It's part of the director and I'm going to make sure what exactly is the tripod set.
That means that as we start to see the impact on our bills and again, what we're going to see in
our next billing cycle, of course, is just the use and the most of the use.
But we do have programs out there that you really encourage customers, thank you very much.
It's alright if you don't have to plan and sign up, you know, that cost, it's spread out, you just find out how to use more time.
And you can also, if you've got the single month that you just have signed something you can plan to do.
Do your vines as you can set the contract so you can just say that amount of time
If you have to work with our customer service folks, and they will be more than happy with the look at the individual scenarios
But this is your account and work with you to grab and explain my work best for you.
She's really always advisable since she's really known as high-strips level.
I'm just going to call those folks, and I'm going to talk for two, six, six, eight, five, and then see what they can do it up the out
But I just wanted to make sure we're still talking about this, and we're going to do it to the forefront, and we'll probably have enough date, different times and weeks until we get through it.
So we just got to try and call them.
But I'll definitely say out of the afternoon questions.
I'd like to go.
In 16, the meeting will be continued with the Bank of Rome, and the meeting will start with the purpose of executive session.